[EPIC]⚡ I hate California. I want to go to the East Coast.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I want to go where culture is, like New York.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 How in the world did I raise such a scene off?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Or at least Connecticut or New Hampshire,
[EPIC]⚡ where writers live in the woods.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 How did you get into those schools anyway?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Mom!
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You should just go to City College.
[EPIC]⚡ You know, with your work ethic,
[DIALOGUE]🗣 just go to City College and then to jail,
[EPIC]⚡ and then back to City College,
[DIALOGUE]🗣 and then maybe you'd learn to pull yourself off
[DIALOGUE]🗣 and not expect everybody to do everything.
[EPIC]⚡ Ahh!
[EPIC]⚡ Lady Bird, is that your given name?
[EPIC]⚡ Yeah.
[EPIC]⚡ Why is it in quotes?
[EPIC]⚡ I gave it to myself. It's given to me by me.
[EPIC]⚡ Lady Bird always says that she lives on the wrong side of
[EPIC]⚡ the tracks,
[EPIC]⚡ but I always thought that that was like a metaphor.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 But there are actual train tracks.
[EPIC]⚡ What she did was very baller.
[EPIC]⚡ It was very anarchist.
[EPIC]⚡ Put the magazine back!
[EPIC]⚡ She has a big heart, your mom.
[EPIC]⚡ She's warm, but she's also kind of scary.
[EPIC]⚡ You can't be scary and warm.
[EPIC]⚡ I think you can. Your mom is.
[EPIC]⚡ So, you're not interested in any Catholic colleges?
[EPIC]⚡ No way.
[EPIC]⚡ I want schools like Yale, but not Yale,
[EPIC]⚡ because I probably couldn't get in.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You definitely couldn't get in.
[EPIC]⚡ Does mom hate me?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 If you're tired, we can sit down.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm not tired.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You're dragging your feet.
[EPIC]⚡ You are so infuriating.
[EPIC]⚡ Will you stop yelling?
[EPIC]⚡ I'm not yelling.
[EPIC]⚡ Oh, it's perfect.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Do you love it?
[EPIC]⚡ You both have such strong personalities.
[EPIC]⚡ When is a normal time to have sex?
[EPIC]⚡ You're having sex?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm right here.
[EPIC]⚡ I just wanted it to be special.
[EPIC]⚡ Why are you going to have so much
[EPIC]⚡ on special sex in your life?
[EPIC]⚡ We're afraid that we will never escape our past.
[EPIC]⚡ Whatever we give you is never enough.
[EPIC]⚡ It's never enough.
[EPIC]⚡ It is enough.
[EPIC]⚡ We're afraid of what the future will bring.
[EPIC]⚡ We're afraid we won't be loved.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You can't do anything unless you're the center of attention.
[EPIC]⚡ We won't be liked.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Yeah, well, you know your mom's tits.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 They're totally fake.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 She made one bad decision in 19.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Two bad decisions.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 And we won't succeed.
[EPIC]⚡ I want you to be the very best version of yourself that
[EPIC]⚡ you can be.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 What if this is the best version?
[EPIC]⚡ What I'd really like is to be on math Olympiad.
[EPIC]⚡ But math isn't something you're terribly strong in.
[HAPPY]😊 That we know of yet.